{
    "subject": "resource/The_Score_Group",
    "predicate": "ontology/location",
    "object": "resource/Miami",
    "human_readable": "The Score Group is located in Miami.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9699530601501465,
            "question": "Is The Score Group based in Miami?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7537420392036438,
            "question": "Where is The Score Group located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6411060094833374,
            "question": "Can you tell me the city where The Score Group is situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4548080563545227,
            "question": "What is the location of The Score Group's headquarters?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42795059084892273,
            "question": "In what city does The Score Group operate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36654308438301086,
            "question": "To what city is The Score Group affiliated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2424040138721466,
            "question": "Where can you find The Score Group's offices?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22978368401527405,
            "question": "What US city houses The Score Group?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2246631681919098,
            "question": "If you wanted to visit The Score Group's offices, where would you go?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.212323859333992,
            "question": "What is the base of operations for The Score Group?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Score Group is located in Miami.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6615_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If you wanted to visit The Score Group's offices, where would you go?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6615_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What US city houses The Score Group?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6615_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where can you find The Score Group's offices?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6615_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6615_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6615_120.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6615_128.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6615_130.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6615_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6615_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6615_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6615_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6615_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6615_49.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here's the evaluation of the triple \"The Score Group is located in Miami\":\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThis answer is correct because according to the text in file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6615/re-ranker-msmarco/41.txt, it is stated that:\n\nQ Where is The Score Group located?\n\nA The Score Group is located at 5001 SW 74th Ct, Miami, FL 33155\n\nThis indicates that The Score Group has a location in Miami, Florida."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe context information confirms that \"The Score Group\" is located at \"5001 SW 74th Ct, Miami, FL 33155\". Therefore, the statement \"The Score Group is located in Miami\" is supported by the provided documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}